1．这两位年迈的得州百万富翁被精密电子
1. The two elderly Texas millionaires were impressed by the sophisticated electronic
窃听设备深深打动了。
eavesdropping equipment.
2．这两位年迈的得州百万富翁被精密电子
2. The two elderly Texas millionaires were impressed by the sophisticated electronic
窃听设备深深打动了。
eavesdropping equipment.
3．此刻，这两位年迈的得州百万富翁正被
3. At the moment, the two elderly Texas millionaires are being impressed by the
精密电子窃听设备深深打动。
sophisticated electronic eavesdropping equipment.
4．这两位年迈的得州百万富翁将被精密的
4. The two elderly Texas millionaires will be impressed by the sophisticated
电子窃听设备深深打动。
electronic eavesdropping equipment.
5．这两位年迈的得州百万富翁将会被精密的
5. The two elderly Texas millionaires would be impressed by the sophisticated
电子窃听设备打动，前提是它有更多实际用途
electronic eavesdropping equipment if there were more practical applications for
的话。
it.
6．这两位年迈的得州百万富翁曾被精密的
6. The two elderly Texas millionaires that had been impressed by the sophisticated
电子窃听设备打动，前提是它曾有更多实际用途
electronic eavesdropping equipment if there had been more practical applications
的话。
for it.
7．这两位年迈的得州百万富翁一直深受
7. The two elderly Texas millionaires that have been so impressed by the
精密电子窃听设备的影响，如今正研究一项新
sophisticated electronic eavesdropping equipment are now researching a new
计划。
program.
8．这两位年迈的得州百万富翁早已被精密的
8. The two elderly Texas millionaires have been impressed by the sophisticated
电子窃听设备深深打动很久了。
electronic eavesdropping equipment for a long time now.
9．这两位年迈的得州百万富翁早已被精密的
9. The two elderly Texas millionaires had been impressed by the sophisticated
电子窃听设备打动，早在盗窃案被挫败之前。
electronic eavesdropping equipment long before the burglary was thwarted.
10．这两位年迈的得州百万富翁将会被精密电子窃听设备彻底打动，等我完成自己的
10. The two elderly Texas millionaires will have been thoroughly impressed by the
……
sophisticated electronic eavesdropping equipment by the time I've done my
11．这两位年迈的得州百万富翁应该被精密的
The two elderly Texas millionaires ought to be impressed by the sophisticated
电子
electronic
窃听设备打动。12．这两位年迈的百万富翁应该被
eavesdropping equipment. Twelve, the two elderly millionaires should be impressed
精密电子窃听设备打动。
by the sophisticated electronic eavesdropping equipment.
13．这两位年迈的得州百万富翁不该被精密的
Thirteen, the two elderly Texas millionaires shouldn't be too impressed by
电子窃听设备打动得太深。
the sophisticated sophisticated electronic eavesdropping equipment.
14．这两位年迈的得州百万富翁本应被
14. The two elderly Texas millionaires should have been impressed by the
精密电子窃听设备打动。
sophisticated electronic eavesdropping equipment.
15．考虑到这种情况，这两位年迈的得州百万富翁本不该
15. Given the circumstances, the two elderly Texas millionaires shouldn't have
被精密电子窃听设备深深打动。
been that impressed by the sophisticated electronic eavesdropping equipment.
16．我们认为这两位年迈的得州百万富翁很可能被
16. We think that the two elderly Texas millionaires could easily be impressed by
精密电子窃听设备打动。
the sophisticated electronic eavesdropping equipment.
17．无论我们做什么，这两位年迈的得州百万富翁都不可能被
17. No matter what we did, the two elderly Texas millionaires couldn't be impressed
即便最精密的电子窃听设备打动。
by even the most sophisticated electronic eavesdropping equipment.
18．两位年迈的得州百万富翁本可能已被精密的
18. Two elderly Texas millionaires could have been impressed by the sophisticated
电子窃听设备打动，但我们不确定。
electronic eavesdropping equipment, but we're not sure.
19．这两位年迈的得州百万富翁不可能已被
19. The two elderly Texas millionaires couldn't have been impressed by the
精密电子窃听设备打动，因为他们五
sophisticated electronic eavesdropping equipment because they left after five
分钟后才离开。
minutes.
20．这两位年迈的得州百万富翁这次可能会被精密的
20. The two elderly Texas millionaires might be impressed by the sophisticated
电子窃听设备打动。
electronic electronic eavesdropping equipment this time around.
21．这两位年迈的得州百万富翁本可能已被
21. The two elderly Texas millionaires might have been impressed by the
精密电子窃听设备打动，但他们没有表示
sophisticated electronic eavesdropping equipment, but they gave no indication one
无论哪种看法。
way or the other.
22．这两位年迈的得州百万富翁一定是被精密的
22. The two elderly Texas millionaires must be impressed by the sophisticated
电子窃听设备打动了，因为他们正在考虑一笔大订单。
electronic eavesdropping equipment because they're considering a huge order.
23．这两位年迈的得州百万富翁一定已经被
23. The two elderly Texas millionaires must have been impressed by the
精密电子窃听设备打动，因为他们订购了这么多
sophisticated electronic eavesdropping equipment because they ordered so much of
这种设备。
it.
24．这两位年迈的得州百万富翁可以被精密的
24. The two elderly Texas millionaires can be impressed by the sophisticated
电子窃听设备打动，因为他们不太了解
electronic eavesdropping equipment because they don't know much about
25.
25．这两位年迈的得州百万富翁不可能被精密的
The two elderly Texas millionaires can't be impressed by the sophisticated
电子窃听设备打动，因为他们发明了最先进的
electronic eavesdropping equipment because they invented most of the state-of-the-art
现有技术。
technology currently available.